- 모니카는?
- 오늘 저녁
- Where's Mon?
- She's at home..
레이첼 생일파티 때문에
집안 장식하고 있어
putting up decorations
for Rachel's birthday party tonight.
- 안도와줘도 돼?
- 도와주려고 했는데
- You're not helping?
- I tried..
헬륨가스 마시고 노래부르는건
도움이 안되나봐
but apparently singing "I Will Survive"
in a helium voice, not helping.
- 안녕
- 어서와
- Hey, guys.
- Hey.
쉿! 작게 말해! 건터가 알면
와서 포옹할거야!
Don't say that loud.
Gunther's gonna want to hug me.
좋은 소식이야
우리 유모 구했어!
Good news, everyone.
We finally found a nanny.
인사해, 몰리야
친구 챈들러와 조이예요
- This is Molly. Molly, Chandler, Joey.
- Hi.
안녕하세요?
저런, 누가 짜증이 좀 났는걸?
Somebody's getting a little fussy.
맞아, 나 짜증났어!
쿠키 주문했는데 7분째 안나오잖아
You're damn right I am. I've been
waiting for a cookie for seven minutes.
오, 엠마 데리고 밖에 나가야겠다
Okay. You know what,
I'm just gonna take her outside.
- 여기 있어요, 내가 할게요
- 고마워요
- No, you stay. I'll do it.
- Okay. Thank you.
- 반가웠어요
- 또 봐요
- Nice to meet you guys.
- Yeah, you too.
- 몰리 참 괜찮지?
- 그래
- Wow, Molly's just great.
- Yeah.
섹시한 유모 만세!
Yes, bravo on the hot nanny.
- 뭐? 정말 몰리가 섹시해?
- 몰라서 물어?
- What? You really think she's hot?
- Are you kidding?
내가 결혼만 안했어도 지금쯤
데이트 신청했다 거절당했을걸
If I wasn't married,
she'd be rejecting me right now.
조이 너두?
Joey?
아주 반갑더라구
How do you think she's doing?
몰리가 섹시하지 않다고
생각하는건 나뿐인가? 로스?
Am I the only one that doesn't think
she's hot? Ross?
글쎄, 난..
매력이 없는건 아니지만..
- I mean, she's not unattractive, but..
- Right.
섹시하다고는..
but hot?
고마워
Thank you.
레이첼 갔으니까 사실대로 말해
Now that Rachel's gone?
죽이지!
나 어제 밤새 몸부림쳤잖아!
So hot, I cried myself to sleep
last night.
프렌즈 시즌 9
'피비의 생쥐'
페루의 수도가 어디죠?
Hey, Mike,
what's the capital of Peru?
- 리마
- 아닌데?
- Lima.
- No.
V로 시작해서 X로 끝나고
It starts with a V
and ends with an X.
가운데 T-O가 들어갈것 같은데
And hopefully with a T-O
in the middle.
생각해보니까
페루의 수도는 VTOX예요
You know, come to think of it,
the capital of Peru is "Vtox."
- 오, 맙소사!
- 왜요?
- Oh, God!
- What?
놀라게 하고 싶진 않지만
Okay. I don't want to freak you out
or anything..
찬장속에 쥐가 있어요
but I just saw a rat
in your cupboard.
알아요
밥이에요
Oh, yeah. No, that's Bob.
피비가 키우는 거예요?
Well, he's your pet rat?
키운다기 보다 가끔 먹을걸
Well, not so much a pet as, you know,
an occasional visitor..
나눠주는 방문객이죠
말하자면 산타처럼요
who I put food out for.
Kind of like Santa.
물론 산타는 과자 접시에
응가하는 법이 없지만
Except Santa doesn't poop
on the plate of cookies.
집에 쥐가 있으면 안돼요
아주 비위생적이라구요
You can't keep a rat in your apartment.
They're unsanitary.
렙토스피라 병과
한타바이러스를 옮겨요
I mean, they transmit leptospirosis
and hantavirus.
- 그게 뭔데요?
- 잘 모르지만
- What are those?
- I don't know..
기분 좋은게 아닌건 분명해요
but they don't sound
like spa treatments.
- 없애버려야 해요
- 마이크가
- You have to get rid of it.
- Okay, fine.
정 원한다면 밥을 없앨게요
If it means that much to you,
I'll get rid of Bob.
고마워요
Thank you.
뭐가 징그럽다는 거지?
밥의 과자는 잘도 먹으면서
It's so weird you think he's so gross,
yet you're willing to eat his crackers.
- 안녕하세요?
- 왔어요?
- Hello.
어제 프리젠테이션 하는동안
Gavin, I just want to say
thank you again..
엠마 봐줘서 정말 고마워요
for watching Emma yesterday
during the presentation.
진심으로 사과할게요
I really owe you an apology.
- 왜요?
- 처음엔 개빈이
- For what?
- When we first met, you know..
아주 오만하고 뻔뻔하고
재수 없다고 생각했어요
I thought you were pompous
and arrogant and obnoxious.
그게 사과예요?
Is this your first apology?
아뇨, 첫 인상은 별 의미가
없다는 말을 하려는 거예요
No, I just mean, you know,
first impressions don't mean anything.
좋은분 같아요
함부로 판단해서 미안하구요
And I think you're a really good guy.
And I'm sorry that I misjudged you.
- 안녕?
- 안녕
- Morning.
- Hello.
새로운 마음으로
새로 시작하자구요
But you know what?
Hey, new day, new leaf.
난 정말 너무나 행복..
I am just really, really happy..
헤더의 엉덩이 감상이
더 중요한 모양이니
I'm sorry. Obviously, Heather's ass
has something more important to say..
끝날 때까지 기다릴게요
so I'll just wait till it's finished.
- 무슨 뜻이죠?
- 남은 기껏 사과하고 있는데
- What?
- I was giving you an apology..
여자 몸매나 감상했잖아요!
and you were totally
checking her out.
감상한게 아녜요, 패션계에서
일하니까 치마를 본거예요
I wasn't. I'm in fashion.
I was looking at her skirt.
바지였나? 엉덩이 아래는
잘 안봤거든요
Or was it pants? I didn't really see
what happened below the ass area.
당신이란 사람
정말 싫군요
Wow, you are really..
You're really a creep.
내가 그 여자 쳐다보건 말건
무슨 상관이죠?
What do you care
if I was looking at her?
질투해요?
Are you jealous?
네! 질투해요!
Oh, yeah. I'm jealous.
"오, 개빈, 제발
내 엉덩이도 봐줘요!"
"Oh, Gavin. Please,
please look at my ass."
쳐다보지 말아요!
Stop looking at my ass!
당신의 행동은 옳지 않아요
I mean, I just think
you are totally inappropriate. Okay?
여긴 회사라구요!
헤더는 당신 부하직원이구요!
This is a work environment.
She's your subordinate.
당신이 옛날 비서 태그와
사귀었던건 괜찮구요?
But it was okay when you
slept with your old assistant, Tag?
그건 두가지 점에서
경우가 달라요!
That is totally different
for two reasons.
첫째, 난 개빈이 그일을
알고 있는줄 몰랐어요
One: I didn't know
that you knew that.
둘째, 난 태그 엉덩이를
쳐다보는 짓은 안했어요!
And two: I wasn't some creep
staring at his ass.
우린 아주 깊고 의미있는
관계였다구요!
We had a.. We had a deep,
meaningful relationship.
태그의 성이 뭐였죠?
What was Tag's last name?
그건..
It was..
오, 이런!
Oh, my God.
태그는.. 성이 없었어요!
He didn't.. He didn't..
He didn't have a last name.
그냥 태그였다구요
가수 셰어나
It was just Tag, you know,
like Cher or..
성경의 모세처럼
you know, Moses.
그러나 깊고 의미 있는
관계였단 말이죠?
But it was a deep,
meaningful relationship.
당신에 대한 내 처음 판단이
옳았어요
You know what? My first impression
of you was absolutely right.
건방지고 뻔뻔하고..
모건! 맞아요!
You are arrogant. You are pompous.
Morgan! Morgan!
- 태그의 성은 모건이었어요!
- 존스였어요
- Tag's last name was Morgan!
- It was Jones.
당신이 태그 애인이라도 돼요?
What are you, his boyfriend?
나도 몰리 같은 유모가
있으면 좋겠어요
- Man, I wish I had a nanny like you.
- You mean when you were a baby?
아기였을때 말이죠?
물론이죠
Sure.
그만좀 쳐다볼래?
Would you stop staring at her?
안쳐다봤어
I wasn't staring.
곁눈질했지
I was leering.
대체 왜들 그래?
What's the big deal with her?
너무 뻔한 미녀 아냐?
Maybe she's attractive
in an obvious kind of way.
맞아, 뻔한건 안좋아
Yeah, obvious beauty's the worst.
그냥 눈앞에 굴러 들어오는건
재미가 없지
You know, when it's right there
in your face.
난 매력적인 사람을
내 힘으로 찾고 싶어
Me, I like to have to work
to find someone attractive.
그래야 보람이 있지
Makes me feel like I earned it.
조이가 몰리랑
잘되어 가는것 같은데?
Looks like Joey's doing all right
with her.
조이한테 여자를 다 양보하고
Yeah. Hey, that was nice of you guys
to back off..
두사람 참 착하네
and let Joey get the girl for once.
- 엠마 집으로 데려갈게요
- 일 끝나면 바로 갈게요
- I'm gonna take her to the apartment.
- Okay. I'll be home right after work.
- 네
- 우리 엠마 웸마 뎀마 안녕!
- Okay.
- Okay, bye, Emma.
사랑해, 우리 귀염둥이!
I love you.
갈게요
- Bye.
그런 아기말투에 대해
내가 한마디 하겠는데
They've elected me to talk to you
about the baby talk.
별로 듣기 안좋아
It's not so good.
난 좋던데요?
I think it's sweet.
안녕, 엠마 웸마 뎀마!
Bye, Emma!
조이, 부탁인데, 제발 몰리한테
작업 들어가지 말아줘
Hey, listen, Joey. About Molly, I would
really prefer if you didn't go after her.
왜?
- Why not?
- It took months to find a good nanny.
좋은 유모 찾는데
거의 한달이나 걸렸어
몰리 그만두는일
생기는건 원치 않는다구
And I wouldn't want anything to,
you know, drive her away.
내가 몰리랑 잔뒤
So you think I'm just
gonna sleep with her..
전화 안해서
불편해지기라도 할까봐 그래?
and never call her again, and
things are gonna get uncomfortable?
하긴 틀린 말도 아니지
Yeah, that sounds about right.
여자들 널렸잖아
Come on, there are plenty
of other women out there.
몰리는 잊어버려
몰리는 접근금지야
Just forget about her, okay?
She's off-limits.
야! 그런 말은 대체
뭐하러 하는거야?
Oh, man! What'd you have to go
and say that for?
접근금지라고 하니까
더 접근하고 싶잖아!
Now that you told me I can't have her,
makes me want her even more!
- 너 애냐?
- 그래!
- What are you, a child?
- Yes!
사실이야, 어린애 같지
벤처럼 말야!
It's true.
He's like a little boy, like Ben.
슈퍼 울트라 초특급
바람둥이 벤이라고 생각하면돼
Just think of him
as a really, really, really horny Ben.
싫어!
No!
조이, 제발 날봐서 참아줘
Look, Joey, come on now.
For me, please.
넘치는 네 에너지를
다른 사람한테 쏟으라구
Just try to focus your sexual energy
on someone else.
알았어
Fine.
나 집에 갈래
Take me home.
내가 맘에 드니?
Do you want a piece of this?
- 안녕, 마이크?
- 어서와요
- Hey, Mikey.
- Hey, Phoebe.
- 뭐해요?
- 쥐덫 놓고 있어요
- What are you doing?
- Setting rattraps.
밥 죽이려구요?
- To kill Bob?
- No. No, to test his neck strength.
아니, 밥의 목 힘이
얼마나 센지 보려구요
안돼요! 죽이지 말아요
난 잡아서 친구들
No, I don't want to kill him.
I thought we were gonna capture him..
만날수 있는
시골에 놔주고 싶어요
and, you know, set him free
in the countryside..
귀여운 주머니쥐나
where he could meet
a friendly possum..
건방진 올빼미나..
and a wisecracking owl.
- 알았어요, 쥐덫 치울게요
- 난 밥을 찾아서 잡을게요
- Okay, okay. I'll throw away the traps.
- All right, I'll find Bob. I'll get him.
밥? 밥?
Bob? Bob?
로버트?
Robert?
잠깐, 소리가 난것 같아요
Wait, I think I hear him.
어머나! 밥이 새끼를 낳았네!
밥이 엄마가 됐어요!
Oh, my God! Bob had babies!
Bob's a mom!
이름을 새로 지어야겠네요
We'll have to think of a new name.
왜요? 밥이란 이름
여자이름으로 좋은데
I don't know,
I kind of like "Bob" for a girl.
아뇨, 내말은..
No, no. I mean, I'm not sure that we..
어떡해! 밥이 죽었나봐!
Oh, my God. We killed Bob?
밥이 아니라
다른 쥐일 수도 있어요
Well, maybe it wasn't Bob.
Maybe it was a mouse.
수지?
Susie?
그게 다야?
That's it?
끝이야?
It's over?
J.R.을 누가 죽였어?
Who shot J.R.?
하루 빨리 취직해야 한다니깐
I have got to get a job.
방가!
What's up?
철지난 유행어는 참아주라
Seriously, dude. Three years ago.
부탁좀 하자
나 없는동안
Listen, can you do me a favor?
I'm gonna be out today.
조이 좀 감시할래?
Can you keep an eye on Joey..
몰리하고 아무일
안생기게 말야
make sure nothing happens
between him and Molly?
- 조이 못 믿어?
- 아까 조이랑
- You don't trust him?
- Well, no.
목소리 비슷한 아줌마가 전화해서
Some woman who sounded
a lot like Joey called earlier..
자기 딸 바꿔달라더라
딸이 "섹시한 유모"래
and asked for her daughter,
the "hot nanny."
나더러 감시하라는거
장기적인 계획이야?
Is this your long-term plan,
for me to run interference?
나 당장이라도
취직할지 모르는데
Because I could get a job any day now.
그래, 당장 뭔가 될것 같은
분위기가 확 풍긴다
You do appear right on the cusp
of something.
1, 2주일이면 시들해질 거야
Look, come on, man. I'm sure
he'll lose interest in a week or two..
며칠만 부탁할게
but for now, could you please
just do this for me?
알았어, 하지만 잘 안돼도
날 탓하지마
Fine, but don't blame me
if it doesn't work.
잘 알겠지만
조이는 일단 마음먹으면
Because you know once Joey
sets his mind on something..
대체로 침대까지
가고 마는 애잖아
more often than not,
he's going to have sex with it.
무슨수를 써서라도
막아야해
Well, I mean,
we've gotta do something. Okay?
몰리같이 좋은 유모는 나무에
주렁주렁 열리는게 아냐
Nannies like her don't grow on trees.
- 그 나무 상상하니?
- 그래, 맞아
- Picturing that tree?
- I am, yes.
어디가?
Where you going, Joe?
산책하러
For a walk.
같이 갈까?
You mind if I join you?
혼자 갔으면 좋겠는데?
생각들좀 정리하고 싶어서
Actually, I'd rather be alone. You know,
I really need to organize my thoughts.
생각 '들'?
Your thoughts?
단수가 아니고 복수야?
Plural?
그래!
오로지 한가지 생각뿐이다!
All right, fine.
I only have one thought.
섹시한 유모!
그 유모 만나러 가야겠어!
It's about the hot nanny!
I gotta see her!
- 안됐지만 널 가게 둘순 없어
- 몰리 만나지 말라구?
- I'm afraid I can't let you do that, Joe.
- Now you're saying I can't see her?
너무 한다!
무슨 금단의 열매도 아니고!
You're killing me! She's forbidden fruit!
It's like, like..
몰리는 공주고
난 마부가 된것 같아!
like she's the princess
and I'm the stable boy.
이해해, 세상에서
가장 아름다운 여자지만..
Look, I know. She's the most
beautiful woman in the world.
다 들린다!
I can hear you.
자기야, 내 베개랑 이불
소파에 꺼내줄래?
Could you set my pillow and blanket
on the couch for me, please?
대체 왜 이러는 거야?
Why are you doing this, huh?
로스가 몰리 만나지
못하게 막으라고 했니?
Did Ross tell you not to let me
go over there?
솔직히 말하면 그래
그러니까 너 보낼수 없어!
Yes, as a matter of fact, he did.
So I can't let you go.
흥! 재미있군
장애물까지 있네
Interesting. Now there are obstacles.
세상에 맞서 싸우는 몰리와 나!
Hot nanny and me against the world!
위대한 문학소설 감이군
This is the stuff great novels
are made of.
- 위대한 문학소설?
- 알았어! 중급 포르노!
- Great novels?
- Fine. Mediocre porn.
- 개빈 미첼 사무실입니다
- 레이첼 그린 사무실이에요
- Gavin Mitchell's office.
- Rachel Greene's office.
이리줘요!
Give me that phone.
레이첼 그린입니다
무슨 일이시죠?
Hello, this is Rachel Greene.
How can I help you?
알겠습니다
아드님 바꿔드리죠
Okay then.
I'll pass you back to your son.
엄마?
아뇨, 비서예요
Hey, Mom.
No, that's just my secretary.
어, 개빈, 잠깐만요
물어볼게 있어요
Excuse me, Gavin.
I have a question I need to ask you.
엄마, 이따 전화할게요
Mom, I'll call you later. Yeah.
- 뭐죠?
- 그렇게 엉덩이 쳐다보는게 좋으면
- Yes?
- If you like looking at butts so much..
거울을 보지 그래요?
why don't you just go
look in a mirror?
드디어 말했군요!
Thank God you finally said that.
세시간 전에
노트에 적는걸 봤거든요
I saw you make a note on your pad
three hours ago.
- 내가 많이 거슬리죠?
- 아뇨
- Man, I really bug you. Don't I?
- Oh, no. Please..
관심이 없는데
거슬릴 거나 있나요?
I don't care about you
enough to bug me.
지금부터 난 편해질 거예요
In fact, from now on,
I'm going to take the high road..
마마보이 개빈에게 아주 아주
친절해질 거예요
and I'm going to be very, very nice
to you, you mama's boy..
지금부터
starting right now.
- 레이첼?
- 어서와
- Hey, Rach.
- Hi.
- 생일 점심 먹으러 가자
- 가야지
- Ready for your birthday lunch?
- I am.
그전에 말야
여기 아주 유능한
But first, Monica,
I would like to introduce you..
내 동료랑 인사해
무엇보다도
to my very talented colleague
and more importantly..
아주 좋은 친구지
개빈 미첼이야
my wonderful friend, Gavin Mitchell.
- 반가워요
- Pleased to meet you.
오늘 레이첼 생일파티에
올건가요?
Are you coming to Rachel's party?
아냐, 안돼! 개빈은 못와
선약이 있거든
Oh, no, no, no, no. Gavin can't.
He already has plans..
자기 엄마랑 약속하는것 같더라
most likely with his mother.
괜찮습니다, 취소하면 돼요
내 비서 생일파티에 빠질수 없죠
I don't mind. I'll cancel them. I would
never miss my secretary's birthday.
대체 왜 초대한 거야!
저 남자 정말 싫다구!
Why did you invite him?
I can't stand that guy!
- 방금 보니까 친한것 같던데?
- 그런척 한거란 말야
- You were being so nice to him.
- I was faking it.
내가 가짜로 그러는 것도 모르니?
Can't you tell when I'm being fake?
필립스씨, 옷 멋지네요!
Hey, Mr. Phillips. Nice suit.
- 지금 그건 분명히 가짜였어!
- 쉿!
Right there.
That was so fake!
자기야, 참치 타르타르랑
Hey, Chandler, which do you like better..
버섯 엠파나다스 중
어느게 더 맛있어?
the tuna tartare
or the mushroom empanadas?
- 생선회 뭉치 아님 타코?
- 당연히 타코지
- The pile of raw fish, or the tacos?
- Oh, the tacos. Definitely, the tacos.
개빈을 초대하다니 말도 안돼!
I still can't believe you invited Gavin.
정말 꼴도 보기 싫은 사람이라구!
He is just the last person
I want to see.
파티 고맙다구?
천만에! 즐겁게 지내
You're welcome for the party.
I'm glad you're having a good time.
제발 안왔으면 좋겠어
어차피 안올거야, 날 싫어하니까
I hope he doesn't show up.
Of course he won't, the guy hates me.
- 그럴까?
- 뭐?
- Does he?
- What?
널 그렇게 괴롭히는건
널 좋아하기 때문 아닐까?
Maybe he keeps bothering you
so much because he likes you.
1학년때
나 몰래 좋아하던 스키피가
It's like in first grade
when Skippy Lange would push me..
걸핏하면 나
넘어뜨린 것처럼 말야
because he secretly
had a crush on me.
어머, 스키피가 널
좋아한다고 생각했니?
Monica, you think Skippy liked you?
너 넘어뜨릴수 있나 없나
남자애들이 내기한 거였어
Honey, all those boys had a bet
to see if he could knock you over.
엠마가 잠들었어요
집으로 데려갈게요
- She's out. I'm gonna take her home.
- Okay. Thank you.
그래요, 고마워요
안녕, 우리 아기
Bye, sweetheart.
남자들이 몰리의 어디가
그렇게 좋은걸까?
Do you see what all the guys
see in her?
침대로 데려가고 싶잖아
Wouldn't kick her out of bed.
술 그만 마셔야겠다
No more vodka for me.
레이첼? 지금 생일축하 노래
불러줘도 돼?
Hey, Rach. So can I sing
"Happy Birthday" to you now?
- 그럼
- 알았어, 생일 축하..
- Yeah, sure.
- All right.
이따봐
See you later.
레이첼?
누가 구두를 선물했나본데?
Hey, Rach. Somebody got you shoes.
정말? 줘봐!
Give me!
- 으악!
- 어머! 조심해!
- Wow. Wow. Oh, my God!
- Careful! Careful!
내가 키우는 새끼쥐들이란 말야
These are my rat babies!
네, 우린 새끼쥐를 키워요
Yeah. We have rat babies now.
내 생일 파티에
쥐를 가져왔단 말야?
You brought rats
to my birthday party?
심장마비가 이런 느낌이구나
So this is what a stroke feels like.
어쩔수 없었어
얘네 엄마를 죽였거든
Well, I had to bring them.
We killed their mother.
우리가 책임져야해
They're our responsibility now.
계속 봐줘야해, 알잖아
너도 엄마니까
You know, they require constant care.
You should know that, you're a mother.
지금 우리 딸이랑
쥐를 동급으로 보는거야?
Are you comparing my daughter
to a rat?
정확히 쥐 일곱 마리야
No. Seven rats.
집으로 가야겠어요
먹이를 줘야할것 같아
We should take them home.
We need to feed them.
잠깐, 쥐 때문에 내 생일파티
중간에 간다구?
You're gonna leave my party
to take care of a box of rats?
미안해
하지만 난 너와는 달라
Well, I'm sorry, Rachel,
but I'm not like you. Okay?
누구나 다 유모를
쓸수 있는건 아니잖니
Not everyone can afford help.
조이랑 몰리 어디있어?
Hey, where the hell
are Joey and Molly?
잘 감시하랬잖아
I asked you to watch them.
미안해
잠깐 한눈좀 팔았어
I'm sorry. I got a little preoccupied.
일 생기기 전에 막아야해!
Look, we have to stop them
before something happens.
알았어! 가자, 친구!
Right behind you, big guy.
사람들은 연기가 훈련의
So you see, Molly,
what people don't understand..
결과라는걸 이해 못하더군요
아주 열심히 노력해야하죠
is that acting is a discipline.
It takes a lot of hard work.
- 어디서 배웠어요?
- 난 대학 안나왔어요
- So where'd you study?
- I didn't go to college.
- 아뇨, 연기 공부 말예요
- 연기는 배우는게 아녜요
- No, where'd you study acting?
- Molly, people don't study acting.
몰리
잠깐 자리좀 비켜줄래요?
Molly, do you mind giving us
just a minute?
- 그러죠, 엠마 보고 올게요
- 고마워요
- Sure. I'll go check on Emma.
- Thanks.
마부는 절대로 공주를
가질수 없다는 거야?!
Will the stable boy
never get the princess?
어쩔 생각이었는데?
이 소파에서 뒹굴기라도 하게?
What do you think you were gonna do,
have sex with her here on my couch?
아니!
가죽소파는 살이 붙어
No. The leather sticks to my ass.
내가 몰리랑 자고나서
차버릴 거라는
This isn't fair. What makes you think
I'm gonna sleep with her..
증거라도 있어?
and then blow her off, huh?
내가 정말로 몰리를 좋아할 수도
있다는 생각은 안드니?
Can't you guys open your minds to
the possibility that I actually like her..
내가 진심일수도 있잖아
and might want something real?
솔직히 레이첼 이후로
이런 느낌 처음이야
Look, the truth is, I haven't felt
this way about anyone since Rachel.
나 다시는 누군가를
사랑할수 없을것 같았어
Okay?
I didn't think I could ever love again.
- 웃기구 있네!
- 집어쳐!
- Come on!
- Joe!
몰리 있나요?
Hi. Is Molly here?
네, 들어와요
몰리?
Yeah, yeah. Come on in. Molly?
- 왔어? 이쪽은 타비타예요
- 안녕?
- Hey. Guys, this is Tabitha.
- Hey.
- 내일 봐요
- 잘가요
- I'll see you tomorrow.
- Okay.
조이, 문제가 해결된것 같다
Well, Joey, I guess
we have no problem.
내가 제일 좋아하는 동화가
현실로 이루어진것 같아!
It's like my favorite fairy tale
come true.
공주에 마부에
레즈비언까지!
The princess, the stable boy
and the lesbian.
됐어요
마이크는 분유 준비해요
Okay. Okay,
you start preparing the formula..
난 상자 갈아줄게요
and I'll start changing the box.
그리고 나서 바로 재워야겠어요
And then we gotta put them
straight to bed.
요즘 우리 생활은 온통
When did we become
one of those couples..
쥐들 중심으로 돌아가는군요
whose lives revolve around
their rats?
우리가 책임져야 한다는거
잘 알잖아요
Well, you know what?
They're our responsibility now.
그래요
얘들은 우리 책임이에요
Okay, fine.
These rats are our responsibility.
하지만 얘들이 서로 짝짓기 해서
수백 마리가 되면 어쩌죠?
What happens when they mate
and there are hundreds?
짝을 짓다뇨?
전부 친형제 자매들인걸요?
Mate? They're all brothers and sisters.
쥐들한테 그런건 문제가 안돼요
Yeah, not such a problem with rats.
오히려 "내 가족을 사랑하라"
그런 편일 걸요?
No, they're more of a "love the one
you're with" kind of animal.
설마! 정말요?
No. Really?
안돼! 누나한테서 떨어져!
Oh, my.. Get off your sister!
맙소사! 어떡하죠?
Oh, my God. What are we gonna do?
쥐가 일곱 마리나 되는데
The.. We have seven rats.
한마리가
So, what if each of them
has seven rats..
일곱 마리씩만 낳아도..
and then each of those
has seven rats? That's like..
너무 많아 계산도 안돼!
That's math I can't even do!
어쩜 좋죠?
What are we gonna do?
미친소리 같겠지만
Well, I know this is gonna
sound crazy..
쥐들이 우리 삶을 망치게
둬선 안된다고 생각해요
but we could
not let the box of rats ruin our lives.
그래요
마이크 말이 맞아요
Yeah, okay. I guess you're right.
그럼 보내야겠네요
All right, so we should just
give them away.
애들이 있는 좋은 집으로 보냅시다
저지방 쿠키를 먹는 집으로
But to nice families with children
and reduced-fat Wheat Thins.
밥이 제일 좋아했던 거예요
Those were Bob's favorites.
다 잘될거예요
It's gonna be okay.
- 내가 돌았다고 생각하죠?
- 아뇨, 착하다고 생각해요
- You must think I'm crazy.
- No, I think you're sweet.
고마워요, 힘드네요
쥐들을 보낸다 생각하니
Good. This is just so hard.
It's hard for me to let them go.
옛날 아픔이 떠오르네요
I guess it just brings back memories,
you know..
남동생의 세 쌍둥이를 낳아서
보내야 했던 일 말예요
from when I gave birth to my brother's
triplets and I had to give them up.
그얘기 안했던가요?
I haven't told you about that yet,
have I?
파티 고마워
치우는거 도와줄까?
Thanks for the party, honey.
Should I help you clean up?
천만에! 네 파티는 끝났잖아
이제부터는 내 파티야
No way. You had your party.
Now I have mine.
괜찮아?
생일파티가 끝나니까
- Is everything all right?
- I just get bummed..
좀 맥이 빠져서 그래
when my birthday's over.
그래도 기쁜일
하나는 있잖아
Well, at least you have one thing
to be happy about.
재수없는 개빈이
파티에 오지 않은것
That jerk, Gavin, from your office
didn't show up.
나도 그 남자 정말 싫어요
Yeah, I hate him.
그쪽 얘기한거 아녜요
We weren't talking about you.
We were..
- 수습하기엔 너무 늦었지?
- 그래
No. No way to recover. No. Okay.
- 즐거운 파티군요
- 정말 즐거웠어요
- Fun party.
- Well, it was.
일찍 왔으면 봤을 텐데요
이렇게 늦게 오다니..
And you would have seen it
if you didn't show up at..
9시 반밖에 안됐네! 세상에!
정말 따분한 파티였어!
9:30?! God! This party was lame.
그렇게 고마워 할것 없어!
Again, you're welcome!
- 이것만 주고 갈게요
- 선물 가져왔어요? 왜요?
- Look, I'll just give you this and go.
- You bought me a present. Why?
생일파티가 원래 그런 거잖아요
선물이 있고..
Let me explain how birthday parties
usually work. There are presents..
케이크도 있고..
사람들도 좀더 있구요
and a cake,
perhaps a fourth or fifth person.
재수없게 군거
Okay, I..
사과하는 뜻에서
선물 가져 온거예요
I got you the present to make up
for being such a jerk to you.
알았어요, 고마워요
카드도 썼네요
Well, okay. Well, that's very nice.
And you wrote a card.
- "개빈으로부터"
- 진심이에요
- "From Gavin."
- I really mean it.
어머, 예쁘네요!
It's beautiful.
내가 해줄까요?
줘봐요
If you don't mind..?
Let me.
좋은데요? 잘 어울려요
Well, what do you know, it fits.
봐요, 당신도 괜찮은 남자가
될수 있는데 말예요
See, Gavin. You're capable of being
a nice guy.
왜 날 못잡아먹어서 안달이죠?
Why do you give me such a hard time?
글쎄요
I'm not sure.
모니카는 내게 특별한 감정을
느껴서 그런 거라던데요?
Well, Monica seems to think
it's because you have feelings for me.
당신에게 특별한 감정을 느껴요
I do have feelings for you.
정말이에요?
- You do?
- Yes. I feel that you're a little annoying.
그래요, 좀 짜증나는
사람이라고 느끼거든요
이렇다니까!
대체 왜 이러죠?
See, why? Gavin, why?
당신에 대한 생각이
바뀔만 하면 꼭 이렇게..
Right when I'm about to change
my opinion of you, you go and you..
이렇게 하는군요
And you do that.
처음엔 겁이 났어
온몸이 굳어버렸지
챈들러?
여기 뭘두고 온것 같아
Hey. Listen,
I think I left something here.
누가 이걸 두고 갔던데
이거 네거야?
Well, somebody left this.
Is this yours?
아니, 하지만 좋은데?
No, but I like it.
새끼쥐 한마리를 잃어버렸어
No, I think I left one of my rat babies.
저런, 아직 못봤는데
보면 알려줄게
Well, no. I haven't seen it,
but if I do, I'll let you know.
엄마야! 쥐다! 쥐야!
Rat baby! Rat baby! Rat baby!
Rat baby!
아, 그 녀석인가 봐!
Maybe that's him.